We'll be right back.
Say you want to live.
We are your friends!
Shoot him down!
Come on!
Go!
Get moving!
Don't you remember what your mom told you?
You must live, Robin!
Attention evacuees!
The ship is leaving!
Wait! Someone's coming!
It's her!
Isn't that the monster girl?
The monster girl?
Yeah, it is!
Go away!
You're creepy!
Hey!
Now's not the time for that!
Now wait!
That kid's mother, Ovia, was in the newspaper just the other day.
That means she's the daughter of a criminal!
You're right!
If we let her on the ship, it might cause us trouble!
Just leave her!
Don't be ridiculous!
She's just a child!
Hurry up and help her!
Everyone stop!
Don't let that brat on board!
Huh?
She may be a child, but she's still an archaeologist!
That means she's a criminal like the rest of them!
A little girl like that?
If you say so, Chief!
See?
I told you!
Good thing we didn't let her on!
Robin!
Must be CP9!
Damn!
I'll show them!
Chief!
Vice Admiral Saul is coming this way!
Is that so?
Then there was no need to question Ovia about him after all!
Fire!
Now!
Shoot him down!
Ice block!
Partisan!
No!
It's Kuzan!
You!
My, my, my!
This just won't do!
If we let a former Marine stop the Buster Call, we'd look like damn fools!
Shkuzan, wake up! You can't tell me this nonsense is justice!
Pull back now! You know this ain't right! They're just making an example out of Ohara!
Come on, please! You're better than this!
If it's for the good of the world, it has to be done. You can't deny that those scholars are breaking the law, can you?
I won't criticize your sense of justice. There are as many rights and wrongs as there are viewpoints in the world.
However, if you insist on getting in our way, I can't sit back and do nothing.
The evacuation ship was blown up! What happened?
Looks like cannon fire from one of our ships!
It was Vice Admiral Sakazuki!
That idiot. If we're doing this, we have to be thorough.
If even one of those scholars had managed to sneak on board that ship, then all the sacrifices we made today would be in vain.
However small, we cannot allow any evil to thrive.
Is this what you call justice? Can you take pride in something like this?
We went too far! I would never do something like that!
We gotta run, Robin!
This fellow's way too strong for me to fight!
Sol is escaping! He's taking one of the scholars with him!
Ice time, capsule!
Oh no! Sol, are you okay?
Robin, you gotta get out of here!
Don't look back! Just go! If you stay on this island, you'll die! Take my raft and go out to sea!
But what about you?
He's got me, little lady. I'm afraid this is the end. Hurry!
No! Everybody I care about is here!
Now you listen to me. You may be lonely at first, but one day you'll find true friends!
True friends?
Yeah. The sea's a vast place, so I guarantee!
Some day you'll find friends who won't ever leave you!
No matter who you are, ain't no one born into this world to be alone!
It's time to go, Robin! This is goodbye!
When things are bad, do like I taught you!
You remember the laugh, don't you?
Look out! He's behind you!
Daddy, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
Now, ice time.
Oh no!
Daddy, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
Your friends are out there at sea waiting for you, Robin.
All you gotta do is find them.
Share your life with them and never let them go.
Ahh, Ahh, Ahh, Ahh!
Yes!
This is it. We're done for.
So this is the history that mankind has chosen.
Shall we ever learn the error of our ways?
Forgive me, Robin.
I couldn't even leave you with any parting words,
neither is a skull or a mother.
A tree of knowledge! It's falling!
The concept of absolute justice can sometimes drive a man to madness.
I've decided to let you escape.
I'm curious to see what kind of flower will sprout from the seed that's all protected.
You can bear a grudge against whoever you like for this,
but at least you're still alive.
However, I do suggest you keep a low profile.
I've drawn a path for you on the sea with my ice.
If you take the boat and go straight ahead, you'll reach land eventually.
Oh, one last thing.
I'm not your ally.
If you do cause any trouble, I'll be the first person to come after you.
My mom's here! Can you help her?
No one will be saved.
If that pain is too great for you to bear, then you may join them.
This library is the best in the world.
You like to read books?
Today is Robin's birthday!
Happy birthday from us at the library!
Your mama's a wonderful woman.
Our heart is a wonderful place.
And as surely as we believe in the past, we believe in the future that you will inherit.
When you're feeling down, just laugh.
There ain't nothing a good laugh can't fix.
It seems awfully silly to laugh when you're sad.
Don't knock it till you try it!
fifteen fifteen...
The sea's a vast place, so I guarantee someday you'll find friends who won't ever leave you.
Survivors? No, I don't think so.
Hey! Huh? Come here, look at the lake!
What? That's insane!
How did all those books get here?
It can't be a coincidence.
Yeah, this is her!
That's definitely the girl. Where did you find her? Is she captured?
No. We were told to keep watch for a suspicious girl.
We eventually found her on a passenger ship northeast of Ohara.
Unfortunately, she knew what we were after, so she slipped away before we could catch her.
She's got the devil's luck.
Back then, I'm sure I saw her leaving Ohara.
The island was burning to ash, but she somehow made it out alone on a little rowboat.
Of course, I tried to chase her, but all of a sudden, the helm of our boat got stuck like it was frozen in ice.
Either way, Saul probably helped her escape before he died.
A scholar with the ability to read the poneglyphs is dangerous no matter how young she may be.
I don't care what methods you use.
If we don't capture her immediately, then this entire mission will have been for nothing.
79 million berries?
Why does an eight-year-old child have such a high bounty?
They said she's one of the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who are plotting to end the world?
Really?
I heard she's saying six marine battleships, too.
She must have some kind of weird power.
Well, that explains the bounty.
The government forces and navy leaders are searching for her, too.
She probably wants to carry out the same plan as the scholars that were executed.
If she's out for revenge, then no one is safe.
We can't let a child of the devil run wild.
Such a kind girl.
Thank you for helping me out.
Sure.
I'm grateful for any work I can get.
By the way, before we have our dinner, some men are here to see you.
Don't let her get away!
No, give me my money!
I told you where she was hiding, didn't I?
She may be small, but she still works hard.
What's wrong?
Having trouble sleeping?
We have to get up early tomorrow to go to work.
So rest well.
Okay.
She's sweet, but if we keep her around, we could get in serious trouble.
Besides, just look at this bounty.
Honey!
She isn't in her room!
Damn it!
She must have overheard us talking.
Damn it, she, she, she, she.
You're hungry?
Sorry.
Me, too.
Damn it, she, she, she.
Seems we're both wanted by the law, Robin.
I know all about you.
Work for me and I'll make sure you never go hungry.
Captain!
The Marines are after us!
Where did Robin go?
Hand her over, damn it!
Hooray!
That girl is bad luck!
A devil like you shouldn't even exist!
What?
Nico Robin's here?
Where at?
Hunt her down!
Turn her into the government!
I can't believe it.
A poneglyph.
Stay away!
I have nothing to sell to the likes of you!
Look, I'm 16.
I'll do anything.
Please, just allow me to join your group.
You betrayed me, you damn witch!
Nico Robin.
I'd like you to assist me.
I've been told you can read Poneglyphs.
If you trigger a buster call, everything will be destroyed.
That includes all of Eni's lobby.
And most likely, you as well.
Nonsense!
What are you saying?
They wouldn't kill a VIP like me!
I'm not falling for your bluff!
20 years ago, everything was taken from me.
And many innocent lives were lost.
With one push of a button,
they summoned a terrible demon.
Now it rears its head again,
aiming its sights on the friends I've searched so hard to find.
The more that I wish for us to be together,
the more my ugly fate bears its fangs at you.
Even now, no matter how far we sail,
there's an enemy that haunts me at every turn.
Because I'm facing the world,
and all of its darkness.
First it was Aokiji,
and now CP9.
I've dragged you into my troubles twice already!
If it goes on and on like this,
no matter how kind you may be,
someday you'll see me as a burden!
Someday you'll be forced to betray me and throw me away!
That's what I'm most afraid of!
Understand?
That's why I didn't want you to rescue me!
If that's the only future I have,
I'd rather die to save me the pain!
Robin...
I never knew.
I see.
So that's it.
Wahahahaha!
There you have it!
Yep, right on the mark!
What a sorry case!
Even if you make friends,
all you can do is drag them through the mud with you!
Wahahahaha!
You can't win, pirates!
Look at this flag!
This symbol represents the unity of over 100...
We'll see you next time.
When I was a kid, I swore I'd gather a crew,
set out to sea, and become a pirate.
A pirate, just like the man who saved me.
And now, just as he protected me,
I'll protect you too, Robin.
You're one of us.
You're my friend.
I'm gonna save you no matter what.
Let's go!
On the next,
One Piece,
Jump Toward the Falls,
Luffy's Feelings.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!